https://www.behs.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Bishop England High School respects and is committed to protecting your privacy.
Use of Personal Information: We do not collect any personal information unless you voluntarily provide it by sending us e-mail, participating in a survey, or completing an on-line form. Personal information submitted will not be transferred to any non-affiliated third parties.
Log Files: Like most website servers we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. This information is anonymous and cannot be directly linked to individual users. We use this information to analyze web traffic and make decisions about how to make it easier for people to find and navigate our website.
Links: This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Security: Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet. Under no circumstances are credit card numbers permanently stored on our website servers.
Contact Information: If users have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact:
Sidebar
